export const data = [
    {
        question:"Which component is used to compile, debug and execute the java programs?" ,
        option1:"JRE" ,
        option2:"JIT" ,
        option3:"JDK" ,
        option4:"JVM" ,
        ans:3 ,
    },
    {
        question:"Which one of the following is not a Java feature?" ,
        option1:"Object-oriented" ,
        option2:"Use of pointers" ,
        option3:"Portable" ,
        option4:"Dynamic and Extensible" ,
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is not an OOPS concept in Java?" ,
        option1:"Polymorphism" ,
        option2:"Inheritance" ,
        option3:"Compilation" ,
        option4:"Encapsulation" ,
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a type of polymorphism in Java Programming?" ,
        option1:"Multiple polymorphism" ,
        option2:"Compile time polymorphism" ,
        option3:"Multilevel polymorphism" ,
        option4:"Execution time polymorphism" ,
        ans:2 ,
    },
    {
        question:"What is Truncation in Java?" ,
        option1:"Floating-point value assigned to a Floating type" ,
        option2:"Floating-point value assigned to an integer type" ,
        option3:"Integer value assigned to floating type" ,
        option4:"Integer value assigned to floating type" ,
        ans:2 ,
    },
    {
        question:"Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?" ,
        option1:"OutOfMemoryError" ,
        option2:"MemoryError" ,
        option3:"MemoryOutOfBoundsException" ,
        option4:"MemoryFullException" ,
        ans:1 ,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these are selection statements in Java?" ,
        option1:"break" ,
        option2:"continue" ,
        option3:"for()" ,
        option4:"if()" ,
        ans:4 ,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?" ,
        option1:"ArrayList" ,
        option2:"Abstract class" ,
        option3:"Object class" ,
        option4:"String" ,
        ans:3 ,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these packages contains the exception Stack Overflow in Java?" ,
        option1:"java.io" ,
        option2:"java.system" ,
        option3:"java.lang" ,
        option4:"java.util" ,
        ans:3 ,
    },
    {
    question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
    option1:"check",
    option2:"throw",
    option3:"catch",
    option4:"try",
    ans:4
    },
];